

CAM WALLER · UX DESIGNER

I'm an analytical-minded artist with a passion for problem-solving, learning and storytelling in any form. I approach design with creativity, multimedia expertise and years of client management experience to produce solutions that fulfill business needs and deliver superb experiences to their users.

☑ camcreates@gmail.com

camcreates.github.com

@camcreates

(904) 635-7296

Education

User Experience Design **Immersive** General Assembly Washington, DC | 2014-2015

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Animation Savannah College of Art & Design

Savannah, GA | 2004-2008

Skills

- Client Management
 - •Art & Design
 - •User Research
- •Wireframes & Prototyping
- Technical Documentation
 - Animation
 - Object-Oriented Programming

Tools & Languages

- Axure
- OmniGraffle
 - Invision
- Adobe Creative Suite
 - Autodesk Maya
 - •HTML/CSS
 - Javascript
 - Python

Past Projects

UX DESIGNER - SALTER MITCHELL

redesign Website for International Rhino Foundation with focus on user research. information architecture and visual design. Delivered survey results, new persona, sitemap, wireframes, clickable prototype and mockups.

GAME ARTIST & ANIMATOR - HORSE ISLE

Designing and producting art assets, animation and UI elements for casual children's Flash games.

FLASH ANIMATOR & DEVELOPER -DR. MIRACLE'S

Designing and producing custom Flash "lounge" environment including backgrounds, character designs, animation and scripting.

INSTRUCTIONAL DESIGNER -SOCIALMEDIAONLINECLASSES.COM

Design of Instagram 101 class, including lesson copy, graphics and tutorial videos, and several additional class updates.

Professional Experience

INDEPENDENT CONSULTANT

2007-PRESENT

Traveling artist, designer, writer, editor, translator and language tutor

COMMUNITY ORGANIZER - GPHOMESTAY

2014-PRESENT

Jacksonville, FL Community Organizer generating host family leads for international students

INTERN - LABO INTERNATIONAL EXCHANGE FOUNDATION

2012-2013

Intern in Nagoya and Fukuoka offices involved in exchange programs and youth groups

EFL TEACHER - TEACH & LEARN WITH GEORGIA

2010-2011

Volunteer English teacher for the Republic of Georgia's Ministry of Science and Education's rural and urban schools

MANAGING EDITOR - GENXXL

2010

Managing editor and podcast team manager.

CAGE ASSISTANT MANAGER - SAVANNAH COLLEGE OF ART & DESIGN

2007-2008

School of Film and Digiital Media equipment cage monitor and assistant manager